Dramatics Files, 1878-1949
Smith College Archives
- Theater Workshop
  - Apr. 22-23, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Brief Music (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 17-18, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Knight of the Burning Pestle (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Bander-log
  - Dec. 5-6, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Ladies on the Loose (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Theater Workshop
  - Dec. 17, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Riders to the Sea (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Two Sides of the Triangle (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - So Wonderful, In White (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The Layette (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Feb. 12, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Quality Street (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 6-7, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Ladies in Retirement (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Theater Workshop
  - Mar. 13, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - The Clod (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Just No Good (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Still Stands the House (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Curse You, Jack Dalton! (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - May 12, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - A Man Who Married A Dumb Wife (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - World Without End (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Arts Guild
  - May 18, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - The Shoe-maker's Prodigious Wife (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 3-5, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Susan and God (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Departments of Music and Theater
  - Dec. 11-12, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - A.D: 1 --- 33 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Department of Theater (Factory Follies)
  - Mar. 16, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Make with the Maximum (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Department of Theater
  - 1943 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Wake Island (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Dept. of Theater and Dramatic Assoc.
  - Apr. 28-29, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - A Watch on the Rhine (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 10-11, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Cry Havoc (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Department of Theater
  - Dec. 10-11, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Antigone (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Department of Theater (Factory Follies)
  - Feb. 16-17, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Between Whistles (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 9-10, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - The Women (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Department of Theater
  - Apr. 28-29, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - In this Short Spring-- (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Department of Theater
  - Oct. 20, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Underground (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 2 - 3, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Department of Theater
  - Dec. 7-9, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Contact Unlimited (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Dramatic Association
  - Feb. 16 - 17, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The Silver Cord (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Department of Theater
  - Mar. 8- 9, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - A Mirror for Witches (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Apr. 19-20, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - The Three Sisters (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 9-10, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - The Little Foxes (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Department of Theater
  - Dec. 13-15, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Dr. Faustus (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 15-16, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Blithe Spirit (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Department of Theater
  - May 22-24, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Style (Box 16, Folder 10)
- General 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 13-15, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Dear Brutus (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Department of Theater
  - Dec. 12, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Fanny's First Play (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Feb. 20-21, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Home of the Brave (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 20-22, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Riders to the Sea (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Mar. 20-22, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Spreading the News (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Department of Theater
  - Apr. 24-26, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Lodestar (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Apr. 24-26, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - La Giara (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - May 21; June 13-14, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Antigone (Box 16, Folder 19)
- General 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Department of Theater
  - Oct. 30- Nov. 1, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Tartuffe (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 19-22, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Dangerous Corner (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Department of Theater
  - Dec. 10-13, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - E=mc2 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Feb. 12-14, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Rocket to the Moon (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 11-13, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Ladies in Retirement (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Department of Theater
  - May 19, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Skin of Our Teeth (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Oct. 28, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - The Corn is Green (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 17-20, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - The Lady of Larkspur Lotion (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Lord Byron's Love Letter (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - This Property is Condemned (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Department of Theater
  - Dec. 7-11, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Day of the Play (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Feb. 16-19, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Escape (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - May 10-13, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Way of the World (Box 16, Folder 31)
- General 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Department of Theater
  - Nov. 2-5, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Street Scene (Box 16, Folder 33)
- [Faculty Production]
  - Feb. 6, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Double Door (Box 16, Folder 34)
      (see Faculty Shows 40.SH)
- Prompt Books (Box 17)
  - As You Like It [1946?] (Box 17)
  - The Taming of the Shrew n.d. (Box 17)
  - The Pretenders (2 vols.) n.d. (Box 17)
- Prompt Books (Box 18)
  - Hamlet, Prince of Denmark [1956] (Box 18)
  - As You Like It n.d. (Box 18)
  - The Winter's Tale n.d. (Box 18)
- Oversize Box (Box 19)
  - Lawrence House
    - Julius Caesar - music arranged by Helen C. Marble Oct. 2, 1900 (Box 19)